The things you need for the wine competition,
I've prepared them all for you.
Which category do you plan to compete in?
Knowing Lin Wanmei,
even if she's no longer at Gufeng Group,
she'll definitely enter under her own name.
Her strong suit is
the red wine category.
That's the category I'm entering.
Before, you always
pushed me away time and time again.
You should include me this time, right?
You know that
to me, the wine competition
is more than just a contest.
I'm still not including you.
I want to uncover this scar myself
and get over this hurdle.
Look.
My hand used to
be able to feel the gentle,
ticklish touch of a feather.
It could feel the soft
and supple touch of your lips
kissing my fingertips.
I could casually hold it up in selfies
to make a pose.
Now,
it can't feel anything at all.
I'll be your sense of touch
and feel the whole world for you.
Take it.
Allergy medicine.
Who's allergic?
Cheng An.
You've never said you love me.
But your every move shows you love me.
The tannin isn't prominent.
The acidity and sweetness are off.
The aftertaste isn't distinct.
Why is my wine
just not as good as hers?
Tomorrow
is the submission deadline.
I can't find a wine to enter.
I'll never be able to beat Ye Xiaowei.
Wanmei.
Your style is different from hers.
You won't necessarily fail.
You need to be more confident.
Yucheng.
Yucheng, I'm begging you.
Please help me.
Help me one last time.
Just one last time.
I can lose to anyone else,
but I absolutely can't lose to Ye Xiaowei.
If I lose to her,
I'd rather die! Wanmei.
Wanmei.
Don't do anything stupid.
You know
I can never say no to you.
Give me a bottle
of wine that can beat Ye Xiaowei.
Okay.
Get up first.
This is a bottle of 2022 Cabernet Sauvignon.
I used a
highly complex winemaking process
to adjust its sweetness and acidity.
It's very similar to your style.
If you'd like,
take it to the competition.
A rich flavor.
In the aftertaste,
there's actually a hint of smokiness.
Excellent.
This one is excellent.
I spent three years making this wine.
I always used to think
it was my hatred and despair for you.
But look.
It's this bottle.
Amour.
So it's this bottle.
The one you promised back then
but never gave me.
But fortunately,
there's still time.
Once,
this was the stage where my dreams shattered.
Now,
it will witness a
feast of vengeance.
The real storm
has settled in the wine bottles.
This time,
I am returning completely transformed
to step into
the place where I once fell.
Waiting for me?
Master.
I haven't heard that title in a while.
Yeah.
I've called you President Lin
and Auntie Lin,
but today, as Ye Xiaowei,
I will call you one last time...
Master.
None of that matters.
You're nothing but a Loser to me.
People need to look forward.
Your winemaking skills are still stuck in the past,
but I'm no longer
the Ye Xiaowei from three years ago.
It doesn't matter who you are.
Don't forget,
I trained you myself.
Don't think a little fame
means you can turn the tables.
It's time
to let you see what the outside world
is really like.
I've been waiting a long time for this day,
Lin Wanmei.
Today, I will openly and honestly
take back everything, with interest,
that rightfully belongs to me.
I destroyed you once,
and I can destroy you again.
Thank you all for attending
the triennial Red Wine Competition.
This competition is divided into four categories:
Red Wine,
White Wine,
Sparkling Wine, and Sweet Wine.
Next,
we will be judging
the entries in the Red Wine category.
After initial screening by the judges,
from the ten teams in the finals,
we will select today's
first, second, and third place winners.
Additionally,
there is a grand prize for the overall winner,
with a cash prize of
one million yuan.
Next, I invite everyone
to begin tasting Red Wine No. 7.
The one who wins in the end
will definitely be me.
It's a bit early to declare a winner.
Besides, it's only the blind tasting stage.
How do you know which bottle is yours, Master?
Do as I say.
All this money is yours.
If you get this done,
I'll give you three times as much.
If anything goes wrong,
you'll never work in this industry again.
You know what to do.
Okay.
Understood.
I'll swap Ye Xiaowei's wine
with yours.
After fierce competition,
for our first segment,
the top two of the red wine category
seem to have been decided.
Please welcome our judge, Mr. Zhou Yucheng,
to announce this competition's
top three winners for the red wine group.
You act like you've already won.
Three years ago or today,
you'll always be a Loser to me.
Then I'll wait and see.
For this competition,
the champion is
Wine No. 7.
The runner-up is
Wine No. 4.
And third place goes to
Wine No. 9.
International Red Wine Competition:
Your assigned number is Wine No. 4.
Your assigned number is Wine No. 7.
Ye Xiaowei,
I will crush you under my feet.
Congratulations, Wanmei.
Even though you placed second,
you still proved yourself.
What are you talking about?
No. 4 tastes exactly like your bottle.
I've tasted it countless times.
There's no way I'm wrong.
I was actually quite happy
you competed with your own work
instead of using my bottle.
Shut up!
to announce to everyone
the list of winners for this competition.
The champion of the red wine group is
independent contestant,
from Lin Wanmei,
Wanmei!
Please welcome this lovely lady on stage!
The runner-up is from Gufeng Group,
Amour.
Love.
Please welcome Gufeng Group's
Ms. Ye Xiaowei
to the stage to accept the award.
Next, we are about to open
the tasting session for the top ten.
We invite all wine lovers here
to drink to your heart's content.
Wait a minute.
This wine tastes off.
During the wine competition 3 years ago,
there was also an Additive scandal.
It makes the tannin more pronounced,
but it's harmful to the body.
It does taste a bit off.
Wanmei.
You...
Master.
Is winning or losing really that important?
More important than your moral integrity
as a winemaker?
Impossible.
Impossible!
As a sponsor,
I request a review of the results.
After rigorous testing,
in Wine No. 7,
banned substances were indeed found.
You know what?
Wine No. 4 is actually yours.
Once Wine No. 7 was found to be tainted,
the champion would be Wine No. 4.
But unfortunately,
my name is on it.
Using your own wine
to defeat your greed.
How about it, Master?
Are you satisfied with this ending?
Have you made up your mind?
If Lin Wanmei has changed,
even if I lose the bet,
I'll accept it.
It was you.
You set me up.
Let me say a few words.
During the wine competition three years ago,
the exact same thing happened.
Back then,
the winemaker standing in front of me,
Ye Xiaowei,
was framed
using the exact same trick.
Eucalyptus Leaf, which she made
and named after the two of us,
was laced with banned substances
and disqualified.
Meanwhile, the winning wine back then,
Evening Breeze,
ostensibly came from
this winemaker, Lin Wanmei.
But in reality,
it was based on Eucalyptus Leaf
with minor adjustments.
Lin Wanmei
stole the fruits of Ye Xiaowei's labor
to achieve her own glory.
This time,
you repeated your old trick.
Afraid you couldn't match Ye Xiaowei,
so
you swapped the entries.
Do as I say,
and this money is all yours.
Once this is done,
I'll pay you triple.
If anything goes wrong,
you'll never work in this industry again.
You know what to do.
That would mean disqualification.
Exactly.
I thought my skills were inferior,
so I chose to swap the wine.
The honor that truly belonged to me,
I couldn't get.
But what I tried so hard to swap for
just got me disqualified.
What a joke.
This has always been a joke.
I told you
I'd let you drink this wine sooner or later.
I just realized
how beautiful the night view is from here.
You know...
I really envy Ye Xiaowei.
We have similar backgrounds.
She can calmly face
her unbearable past,
and still get Cheng An's love.
She has everything I've ever dreamed of.
But I...
have always struggled between power
and love.
I could never follow my own heart.
If you could live your life over again,
would you still make the same choices?
Envying Ye Xiaowei is one thing,
but I am still me.
Once certain choices are made,
there's no turning back.
Have you ever regretted it?
So many people got hurt because of you.
Died because of you.
From me,
to Chu Yan,
Zhao Yue, and even Wan Niang.
You've ruined so many lives.
Did you ever feel guilt late at night?
Or regret?
Once a move is made,
No regrets.
As for my life,
I never look back.
That's very Lin Wanmei of you.
Good.
Actually, I've learned a lot from you too.
I used to think
good people don't always get rewarded,
and that kindness isn't worth it.
That only bad
and selfish people
can live a good life.
But right now,
I realize more clearly than ever
that the kind of life
anyone wants to live
has nothing to do with their background.
It's about every choice you make.
Lin Wanmei,
since we were once Master and apprentice,
I hope you get to live the life you want.
Ye Xiaowei,
let's say our goodbyes.
Wanmei
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Why are you up here on the roof?
Stay and talk to me.
Okay.
I don't think I've ever
told you about my childhood.
I was born in
Taojia Village, surrounded by grapes.
The hills and fields there
were covered in grapes.
Every day, I'd open my eyes,
only to pick grapes,
plant grapes,
prune branches,
till the soil,
and fertilize.
All year round,
day after day.
But do you know
why I refuse to admit
that I'm a fruit farmer's daughter?
You think I'm afraid of that?
It's because I hate it.
I hate the poverty there,
the backwardness,
the foolishness,
the ignorance.
I hate parents who don't raise kids.
Girls like us who were born there
were nothing but toys
for those men to grope and abuse.
I had no choice.
I could only escape.
I thought as long as I got out,
as long as I was ruthless,
pushed hard, and risked everything,
I could make a name for myself.
Finally,
everything is coming to an end.
Wanmei,
let's go back down first.
Zhou Yucheng,
thank you for loving me.
I know
that only you truly love me.
Have a drink with me.
Okay.
Wanmei
You've always focused solely on fame and wealth.
Love was never something you considered.
In their eyes,
you're hypocritical,
frivolous,
and vicious.
But in my eyes,
you are my love.
Wherever you stand,
is love itself.
I love you.
I love your kindness and hypocrisy.
I love your radiance
and ruthlessness.
I love all your strengths
and flaws even more.
Actually, Lin Wanmei had a pitiful life.
Though she pushed me into the abyss,
she also taught me how to make wine.
So today, regardless of right or wrong,
I came to see her off.
If she could have realized
that there are things in this world
far more precious than fame and wealth,
her ending might not have been like this.
Let's go.
Wanmei
I'm going to turn myself in.
I've done so many terrible things.
I should face justice.
Your bag doesn't have a zipper.
It's not safe to keep your ID in there.
Then where should I put it?
Tell you what,
let me hold onto it.
Here.
Give it here.
Smile.
Look at the camera.
OK
Mrs. Cheng.
Hurry up and give me a like.
Do I really have to remind you?
You don't usually post anything anyway.
But seeing you post today,
you seemed pretty experienced.
How long did you practice in secret?
Wanna know?
Come here.
I'm not telling you.
Childish.
Are you getting tired of me already?
Let me tell you, it's too late.
We already got our marriage certificate.
Bound together for life.
You know?
Who says?
Let me go.
I won't.
Let go.
No.
Xiaowei.
I love you.
What?
I didn't hear you.
I said, I love you.
Welcome.
Welcome to the Roses for An
launch event.
Welcome.
Congratulations. Congratulations.
Stand up straight.
Yes, honey.
Have a taste.
Everyone, please try the wine.
Here you go.
Congratulations on your new journey.
What made you decide
to create this independent wine brand?
Like many people,
I come from a humble background
and have endured life's hardships.
But I've always believed
that as long as you have a dream,
every effort will bear fruit.
So,
for this wine brand of mine,
I hope it's not just
bottles of high-quality wine,
but a symbol
carrying dreams,
hope,
and courage.
May everyone who tastes it
feel the aftertaste of life,
and be able to find
their way forward in adversity.
Finally,
I hope that in your everyday lives,
you can all find your own happiness.
Cheers!
Cheers! Cheers!